selinks.com 2013-05-05

# Sell Links, Buy Text Link Ads. Selinks - Link Building Service

**PRIVACY POLICY**

****  
selinks.com treats your privacy seriously. This section dwells on how selinks.com treats personal information we collect and receive. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
You must be of the full legal age in the country of your residence to be legible to take part in the selinks marketplace.  
selinks.com collects personal information when you register: your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, address, payment system.  
selinks.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except for under the following circumstances:  
•    selinks.com respond to court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
•    selinks.com believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.   
You can edit your Account Information at any time. selinks.com reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to the our service, such as service announcements and administrative messages.   
You can delete your account by requesting the account elimination with our support team.  
CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY  
selinks.com limits access to personal information about you to employees who selinks.com believes reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.   
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
selinks.com may update this policy. selinks.com will notify you about significant changes in the way selinks.com treats personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.   
Security    
selinks.com takes your security seriously and takes reasonable steps to protect your information. No data transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. The following is a summary of the measures selinks.com takes to protect your information:  
•    Secure Socket Layer (SSL)  
selinks.com use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of information, such as financial services information or payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. The information you provide will be stored securely on our servers.   
•    Secure Storage  
selinks.com maintain reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.  
•    Employee Access to Information  
selinks.com limit access to personal information about you to those employees who selinks.com reasonably believes need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
